edisonnation.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy – Edison Nation

Last updated on 1 April 2013 

**EdisonNation.com is committed to protecting information collected through its website. This Privacy Policy outlines how EdisonNation.com collects, uses, and protects personally identifiable user information. Should you choose to provide us with any personally identifiable information, you should feel confident that we will abide by this policy. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and you should check this page periodically for changes. When changes are made, we will do our best to notify you. You may contact EdisonNation.com by calling 704-333-5335 or by emailing info@edisonnation.com should you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy.**

**What information do we collect?**

You may visit EdisonNation.com anonymously. However, if you would like to register, you are required to provide your first and last name and your email address. You may also be requested—but are not required—to provide a physical address, demographic information such as gender, information regarding your education, photographs and videos. We will never ask for your Social Security number.

**How do we use your information?**

Any of the information we collect may be used in one or more of the following ways:

To personalize your experience. Your information helps us to better understand and respond to your situation and needs.

To improve our website. The more we know and understand about our users, the more we can improve our website.

To send periodic emails. The email address you provide will be used to send notices regarding updates to the site, its Terms of Use, and/or this Privacy Policy. We may also use the email address you provide to contact you as needed or required, and to send occasional newsletters. NOTE: If at any time you would like to “Opt Out” of commercial email messages, we provide instructions to do so at the bottom of each email. EdisonNation.com reserves the right to contact its users, without penalty, as required by law.

**How do we protect your information?**

EdisonNation.com and its partners implement a variety of security measures designed specifically to protect user information.

**Do we share your information?**

EdisonNation.com will never sell, share, or trade your personally identifiable information with a third party. Trusted third parties who provide support services for our website may have access to your personally identifiable information, however these third parties agree to abide by this Privacy Policy. EdisonNation.com may disclose personally identifiable information as required by law, to enforce our site’s policies, and/or to protect the rights, property, and safety of other EdisonNation.com users and/or employees.

**Do we use Cookies?**

EdisonNation.com uses Cookies, however no personal information is saved to the cookie.

**How you may control your information?**

You may control or restrict access to your information by not providing any information that’s not required. You may also change, modify, or delete any information that you have provided by following links and instructions provide on our website. EdisonNation.com also allows its users to classify or declassify your user information as public or private, which also helps you to restrict access to your information. Users may also choose to delete registered accounts.

**Will this Privacy Policy changes?**

EdisonNation.com reserves the right to change, modify, or alter this Privacy Policy and will do its best to notify its users by email regarding any changes. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on this page. We recommend that you check this page periodically for changes in the event that we are unable to notify you of such changes.

**Does this Privacy Policy apply to information not collected through the website?**

No. This Privacy Policy only applies to information that we gather through the website EdisonNation.com. Any other information that you provide to EdisonNation.com, EdisonNation, LLC, and its affiliates that is not collected through this website is not subject to this Privacy Policy.

**Consent to this Privacy Policy.**

By accessing and using our site, you consent to and agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Please review our Terms and Conditions for further information regarding EdisonNation.com’s terms of use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability.
